<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Prasanna Natarajan</title>
    <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Prasanna Natarajan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:28:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RoadEye</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/roadeye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:28:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/roadeye/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword Search in Spatial Databases</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/keyword_search_in_spatial_databases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:28:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/keyword_search_in_spatial_databases/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a database of spatial objects, every tuple is associated with certain information represented by keywords. This paper introduces a new type of spatial keyword query, known as the m-closest keywords (mCK) query. The aim of the mCK query is to find tuples which are located in the closest spatial proximity that align with the user-entered keywords. In order to efficiently process mCK queries, a new index is introduced, known as the bR*-tree, which is an extension of the R * tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information Theory and Nueral Coding</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/information_theory_and_nueral_coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:27:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/information_theory_and_nueral_coding/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This goal of this paper is to do a literature review in the intersection of the fields of neural information transfer and information theory – Neural Coding and Information Theory. This paper looks at three papers and pursues this topic with a focus on the Information Theory-related concepts.
The full paper can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Network Data Aggregation and Processing</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/in_network_data_aggregation_and_processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:27:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/in_network_data_aggregation_and_processing/</guid>
      <description>Abstract In this paper, we cover various aspects of in-network data aggregation and processing in wireless sensor networks. We survey existing literature about energy efficiency, security, compression and query processing methods, looking at multiple existing research papers across these domains, identifying and highlighting key research objectives, methodologies and finally discuss how they build upon or improve previously existing solutions. Finally, we discuss future research goals in each of the areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of branch prediction</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/analysis_of_branch_prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 02:42:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/analysis_of_branch_prediction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNU Earthquake Early Warning System</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/snu_eews/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/snu_eews/</guid>
      <description>Crowdsourcing an Earthquake Early Warning System for the Indian Subcontinent (SNU-EEWS) Abstract: Earthquakes are potentially very destructive natural events. The risk from earthquakes is aggravated because they are unpredictable and can cause tremendous loss of life and property within seconds, particularly in dense urban settings. We present our ongoing work to develop a comprehensive earthquake early warning system (EEWS) for the Indian subcontinent. The impetus for this work comes from the fact that India has just 82 seismic stations for a land area of about 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Course Projects</title>
      <link>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/academic_project_undergrad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prasannanatarajan.github.io/project/academic_project_undergrad/</guid>
      <description>Projects (Computer Science) - Under Graduate course work 1. Self-Service Portal for Mobile Application development (RMADP) Description: A rapid mobile application development platform where users can drag and drop components into a mobile screen on the portal and build a complete android/ios application.
Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JS, Vue.js for View layer, which is hosted on an Apache server. STS server for controller layer. MySQL for model layer. Node.js and bash scripts for build server layer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>